Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series IV: Polytechnic, 4386
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 4397
    - Civil Engineering Department, 2009 October; 5131 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Urban Sustainability Center, 2006 September - 2008 September, Undated; 5132 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Jerry Hultin - Grant Proposal, 2006 January-April; 5149 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Urban Sustainability – Drafts, 2009 September; 5133 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Urban Sustainability Presentation – Yale University, 2005 April 6; 5134 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Polytechnic University – 150th Anniversary – Poly Legend, 2004; 5135 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - George Bugliarello's Collection of Accomplishments – 1, Undated; 5136 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - George Bugliarello's Collection of Accomplishments – 2, Undated; 5137 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - George Bugliarello's Collection of Accomplishments – 3, Undated; 5138 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - George Bugliarello's Drafts, 2003-2005; 5139 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Arts and Sciences Engineering Management Course Bulletin, Undated; 5140 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - George Bugliarello Articles / Talks, 1984-2010; 5141 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Poly at a Glance – Pamphlet, 2005; 5142 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Space Planning Committee, 2009 September - 2010 January; 5143 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Faculty, 2002 March; 5144 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Poly Ventures, Undated; 5145 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Center for Technology and Financial Services – Financial Engineering -1, 1994-1997; 5146 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Center for Technology and Financial Services – Financial Engineering - 2, 1994-1997; 5147 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Center for Technology and Financial Services – Financial Engineering -3, 1994-1997; 5148 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Curriculum and Standards Committee, 1994 November 28; 5151 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Jerry Hultin – Howe School of Technology Management – "Securing the Port of New York and New Jersey", 2004 September; 5152 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - "Research at Polytechnic: An Overview", Undated; 5153 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - "Technology", by George Bugliarello – Copy, Undated; 5154 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Jacob's Engineering Group, Inc., 1982 July 27; 5155 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Symbol Technologies Inc. – 2003 Audit Committee Meeting, 2003 April 28; 5156 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Inauguration Scrap book – 1, 1975; 5157 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Inauguration Scrap book – 2, 1975; 5158 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Inauguration Scrap book – 3, 1975; 5159 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Management Reports – Kenneth Brock, 1985-1986; 5160 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Management Reports – Jim Conti, 1985-1986; 5161 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Management Reports – Martha Leonard, 1985-1986; 5162 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Management Reports – Bob Maciag, 1985-1986; 5163 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Management Reports – John Rorer, 1985-1986; 5164 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Management Reports – Sy Scher, 1985-1986; 5165 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Management Reports – Arts & Science Department, 1985-1986; 5166 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Management Reports – Library, 1985-1986; 5167 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Management Reports – Division of Management, 1985-1986; 5168 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Management Reports – R. Thorsen, 1985-1986; 5169 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Management Reports – Academic Departments, 1985-1986; 5170 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Management Reports – Academic Departments, 1985-1986; 5171 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Management Reports – Engineering Department, 1985-1986; 5172 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - C.T.M. – Policy Board Meeting, 2003 October 17; 5173 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - George Bugliarello's Stationary, Undated; 5174 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Clipping – Biotech, 2001 June 11-17; 5175 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Acquisition of Military Significant Western Technology: An Updated, 1985 September; 5176 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - New York University, 2004-2008; 5177 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Tribute to George Bugliarello, 2011; 5178 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – DVD Copies, 2011; 5179 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Program, 2011 April 27; 5180 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Correspondence, 2011 February-April; 5181 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Correspondence, 2011 May; 5182 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Set-Up, 2011 April; 5183 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Guestbook Invoice, 2011 April 4; 5184 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Cancellations, 2011 March-May; 5185 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Correspondence, 2011 March-May; 5186 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Responses, 2011 March; 5187 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - George Bugliarello Memorial – Correspondence, 2011; 5188 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Draft, Undated; 5189 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence – Miscellaneous, 1985-1992; 5190 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration - Miscellaneous, 1975; 5191 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Senator James Buckley Visit, 1975 October 14; 5192 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Executive Committee, 2002-2003; 5193 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Budget, FY88 - CONDIFENTIAL, 1987-1988; 5194 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Brochures, Undated; 5195 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Donald F. Othmer – Chemical Engineering Notes, Newsletter, 1989 Summer; 5196 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Brochures, Undated; 5197 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Hofstra University Earth Week – Urban Sustainability, 2010 February; 5198 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Urban Systems Initiative Director Search, 2009-2011; 5199 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Don Lebell – CONFIDENTIAL, 2009-2010; 5200 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Jerry Hultin – Correspondence, 2010 November; 5201 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - C.T.M. – Bodegas and City Harvest, 2010 September 24; 5202 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Bruce Niswander – U.N. Global Urban Sustainability, 2010 September; 5203 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 2010 Fall; 5204 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 2010 Fall; 5205 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Faculty Activity Report – Chemical Engineering, 2010; 5206 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Center for Urban Sustainability – Proposal, 2008-2009; 5207 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Dr. Kurt Becker, Associate Provost, 2010 August 10; 5208 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Faculty Search Committee – Poly Urban Systems Initiative Director Search, 2009 November - 2010 March; 5209 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Polytechnic Cable – "i2e and the Resurrection of Downtown Brooklyn", 2010 November - 2011 February; 5210 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Dr. Kristen Day – Department of Humanities and Social Sciences, 2010 September 23; 5211 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Board Certificate of Distinguished Service, 1985 June 5; 5651 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Center for Regional Technology, 1975; 5652 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Council on Foreign Relations – Dr. A. George Schillinger, 1994-1997; 5653 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1992 February-March; 5654 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Event Itineraries, 1991 June; 5655 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Faculty Search Committee, 2009 October; 5656 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Finances – New York Times Photo Reprint Invoice, 2000 September, December; 5657 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Paul R. Freeman – Alumnus '48, 2010 November; 5670 (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - Inauguration Poem –"Super-George", 1973; 5658 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - Joseph Jacobs - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges – Nomination, 1989 September - 1992 September; 5659 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Joseph Jacobs - Heinz Award, 1999; 5660 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Jacobs - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994; 5661 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Joseph Jacobs - Miscellaneous, 1995-2004; 5662 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Media Report, 1984 January-February; 5663 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Media Report, 1984 March-April; 5664 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Media Report, 1984 May-December; 5665 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Bala Mulloth – Thesis Defense – CONFIDENTIAL – 1, 2010; 5666 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Bala Mulloth – Thesis Defense – CONFIDENTIAL – 2, 2010; 5667 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - N.S.F. – SUNY Downstate & Poly Joint PhD in Biomedical Engineering, 2006 March; 5668 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Office of Contracts and Grants – Annual Report of Awards, 2000 July - 2001 June; 5669 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - "The Polytechnic Effort: A Self Study Report" – Middle States Association Accreditation Visit, 1982 March 28-31; 5671 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Press – "Engineering Colleges, Legislatures and the Community", 1977; 5672 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Promotional Material, 1973-1990; 5673 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Promotional Material, 1974-1998, Undated; 5674 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Promotional Material, 1991-1996; 5675 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Promotional Material - Events, 1975, 1983-1986; 5676 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Promotional Material - Events, 1990-1991; 5677 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Promotional Material, Undated; 5678 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - University Code of Conduct, 1993 January 26; 5679 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - University Code of Conduct, 1999 July; 5680 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Workshop – "Nanotechnology and Bio-Nanotechnology in Civil Engineering", 2003 December - 2005 October; 5681 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Subseries B: Center for Technology in Merchandising (CTM), 2182
    - Management of Technology and Innovation in Retailing, 1998, Undated; 5682 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Policy Board – Correspondence, 2006 January 31; 5683 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Policy Board – Sears, 1998 May - 2000 August; 5684 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Policy Board Meeting, 2000 June; 5685 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Prospectus – Master, Undated; 5686 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Symbol Technologies – Tech Lab, 1998 September - 2000 January; 5687 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Policy Board, 2000 June; 2183 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Proposal - Revision, 1998 May; 2184 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - "New Material", 1988 September - 1999 February; 2185 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Course description & copy of brochure, 2001 May; 2186 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Prospectus, 2000, Undated; 2187 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Tom Cole & Jerry Miller, 2000 July-October; 2188 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Policy Board Member - Bios, 2002; 2189 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Policy Board - Correspondence, 2002 March; 2190 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Policy Board - Meeting, 2002 January-February; 2191 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Symbol - Budget, Purchase Orders, 1999 February - 2000 October; 2192 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Blair Williams, 2001 December; 2193 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - High School student outreach - Sears Roebuck & Co. - Conference call, 2000 December; 2194 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Garey V. Ellis - Y.E.S. Center, 2000 August; 2195 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - MOTIR 2004 (Management of Technology and Innovation in Retailing), 1999 August - 2004 February; 2196 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Barnes & Noble, 2001 October-November; 2197 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Policy Board Meeting - January 15, 2001, 1999 August - 2001 February; 2198 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Policy Board Meeting - January 29, 2002, 2001 August - 2002 January; 2199 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic Loan, 2000 November - 2001 January; 2200 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Press Piece, 2001 July 6; 2201 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Resumes - RESTRICT, Undated; 2202 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Symbol, 2002 March; 2203 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Website, 2001 July - 2002 July; 2204 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - MOTIR Student Dinner, 2002 December 3; 2205 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - MOTIR Applications - RESTRICT, 2002 May; 2206 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - KMART, 2001 September; 2207 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Tom Cole, 2000 May-October, 2006 January; 2208 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Arthur R. Martinez, CEO & Chairman of Sears Roebuck & Co. - Meeting - February 5, 1999, 1998 September - 1999 February; 2209 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - SAP Retail Solutions visit – January 20, 1999, 1999 January-August; 2210 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Course - Introduction to the Technology and Management of the Supply Chain, 1998 November - 1999 January; 2211 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Advertisement - Draft, 1999 February; 2212 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Internship event - August 28, 2002, 2002 August; 2213 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Policy Board Meeting – September 27, 2001, 2001 April - 2002 January; 2214 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Grant, 1998 July 2; 2215 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Grant - Budget, 1998 September 4; 2216 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - George Schillinger - Conference call, 1998 November 16; 2217 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Technology in Merchandising – Brochure, 1998 September; 2218 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Retired Executive Search, 2000 November-December; 2219 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Arthur C. Martinez, Chairman & CEO, Sears Roebuck & Co. – Merchandising Project Steering Committee Meeting – October 13, 1998, 1998 March-October; 2220 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Proposal – Draft, 1997 December 4; 2221 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Annual Report, 1999 September-October, 2000 October; 2222 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Miscellaneous, 1998 May - 2002 November; 2223 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Symbol – Grant Payments, 1999 January - 2001 April; 2224 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Final Report, 2004 June-July; 2225 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Federated Logistics & Operations – Funding, 2001 March, 2004 June; 2226 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - E-Commerce and New Business Models Seminar – December 13, 1999, 1999 November-December; 2227 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Grant – Miscellaneous, 1998 April - 1999 April; 2228 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 2001 August; 2229 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 January-August; 2230 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Proposal, 1998 April; 2231 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Federated Department Stores Foundation – Donation, 2001 February - 2004 August, Undated; 2232 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Follow up / Status report – Student presentations, 2002 December - 2003 January; 2233 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Sears Roebuck & Co. Grant, 1999 July - 2000 March; 2234 (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - MOTIR – Miscellaneous, 2000 November - 2003 April, Undated; 2235 (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Policy Board Members – Correspondence, 2003 March 10; 2236 (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Policy Board – Meetings, 2001 June - 2004 September; 2237 (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Request for Official Designation as Center for Technology in Supply Chains and Merchandising, 2002 October-November; 2238 (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Workshop Proceedings, 1998 February, March; 2239 (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Ewing Marion Kauffman Foundation, 2004 March-May; 5722 (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Policy Board Meeting, 2001 September 27; 5723 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Michael Greenstein, 2002 August 29; 5724 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1996 August - 1997 February; 5725 (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - "A Program in Technology and Merchandising at Polytechnic University" - Early Draft, 1995 September 13; 5726 (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Book Mailing, 1998 March-April; 5727 (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Workshop of Executives in the Merchandising and Distribution Sectors - Correspondence, 1997 May; 5728 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Workshop Program - Follow Up, 1997 June-July; 5729 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1997 August-November; 5730 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Meeting with A. Martinez, J. Swartz and President Chang, 1997 February 14; 5731 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 July - 1998 June, 2002 September, Undated; 5732 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1996 August - 1998 May; 5733 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Meeting - A. Martinez and President Chang, 1998 March 3; 5734 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C: Leadership Seminar Series, 1994-1996; 1688
    - Joseph Jacobs - Speaker - October 17, 1994, 1994 September-October; 4377 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Clifford Goldsmith - Speaker - October 24, 1994, 1994 October-November; 4367 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Stewart G. Nagler - Speaker - November 14, 1994, 1994 October; 4378 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Horwitch, Mel - Speaker - January 29, 1995, 1995 January 29; 5214 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Donald M. Cox - Speaker - January 30, 1995, 1995 January-February; 4375 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Eleanor Baum - Speaker - February 5, 1995, 1995 February 5; 4382 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Casimir Skrzypczak - Speaker - February 6, 1995, 1994 July - 1995 February; 4356 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Bill Friend - Speaker - February 10, 1995, 1995 January; 4381 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Leonard Berkowitz - Speaker - February 19, 1995, 1995 February 19; 4383 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Georgia Fisanick - Speaker - February 20, 1995, 1994 October - 1995 February; 4358 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Steve Wallach - Speaker - February 27, 1995, 1995 January-February; 4353 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - John G. Puente - Speaker - March 6, 1994, 1994 October - 1994 January; 4379 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Herman Fialkov - Speaker - March 13, 1995, 1994 October - 1995 April; 4368 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Richard W. Foxen - Speaker - March 20, 1995, 1995 March-April; 4373 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - David Dibner - Speaker - March 27, 1995, 1994 November - 1995 March; 4371 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Peter M. Lehrer - Speaker - April 3, 1995, 1995 March-April; 4359 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Harry C. Wechsler - Speaker - April 17, 1995, 1995 February-April; 4374 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Arthur C. Martinez - Speaker - April 17, 1995, 1995 January; 4380 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Steve Greenfield - Speaker - April 24, 1995, 1995 March-May; 4369 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Henry J. Singer - Speaker - April 26, 1995, 1995 January-April; 4370 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - David A. Conklin - Speaker - October 2, 1995, 1995 September-November; 4361 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Eugene J. Fasullo - Speaker - October 9, 1995, 1995 August-December; 4357 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Paul Soros - Speaker - October 23, 1995, 1995 September-November; 4366 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Irene Van Slyke - Speaker - October 30, 1995, 1995 October; 4363 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - John Mayo - Speaker - November 6, 1995, 1995 September-December; 4364 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Senator Frank Padavan - Speaker - November 13, 1995, 1995 September-December; 4365 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Robert Dalziel - Speaker - November 27, 1995, 1995 September-November; 4362 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Invitations to Speakers, 1994 September - 1995 January; 4376 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Seminar Refreshments - Invoice, 1995 January-February; 4360 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Student Registration Forms - RESTRICT, 1995; 4354 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Sign-in Sheet, 1995; 4355 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Sign-In Sheets - RESTRICT, 1995; 4384 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Thank You Notes, 1995 May; 4372 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 August - 1995 September; 4385 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Subseries D: Professional Calendars, 3918
    - Professional Calendar, 1996; 3919 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Professional Calendar, 1997; 3920 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Professional Calendar, 1998; 3921 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Professional Calendar, 2004; 3922 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Professional Calendar, 2005; 5014 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2005; 3923 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Professional Calendar - Grant Budget Status Reports, 2005; 3924 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Professional Calendar, 2007; 3925 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2007; 3926 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Professional Calendar, 2008; 3927 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Professional Calendar, 2009; 3928 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2009; 3929 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Professional Calendar, 2010; 3930 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2010; 3931 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Professional Calendar, 1991; 3932 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Professional Calendar, 2002; 3933 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Professional Calendar, 2003; 3934 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2003; 3935 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Professional Calendar, 2011; 5015 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Professional Calendar, 1999; 3936 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Professional Calendar, 2006; 3937 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Professional Calendar - Miscellaneous Inserts, 2006; 3938 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Professional Calendar, 1992; 3939 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Professional Calendar, 1993; 3940 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Professional Calendar, 1994; 3941 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Professional Calendar, 1995; 3942 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Professional Calendar, 2000; 3943 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Professional Calendar, 2001; 3944 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Suberies E: Urban Sustainability, 5019
    - "A Major Workshop on Engineering Education for Urban Sustainability", 2004 October-November; 5016 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Compliments to Sustainability Class – Notes, Clippings, 2009-2010; 5017 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Notes, Undated; 5018 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - "Integrated Interdisciplinary Program on Urban Sustainability", 2003 July 16; 5020 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - The Sustainable Mobility Project – Full Report – World Business Council for Sustainable Development, 2004; 5021 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Mobility 2001 – World Business Council for Sustainable Development, 5022 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - The Sustainable Mobility Project – Progress Report, 2002 July; 5023 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - "Sustainable Habitats" – NRC Grant, 1995-1996; 5024 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Urban Sustainability Center, 2004 September; 5025 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Center on Emerging Urban Challenges – Presentation, Undated; 5026 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Sustainability Practices Committee – Polytechnic University, 2008 March-September; 5027 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Urban Systems Group – Polytechnic University, 2006 September-October; 5028 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Roberta E. Weisbrod – Partnership for Sustainable Ports, 2009 May-June; 5029 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Sustainability Leadership Certificate – Robert N. Ubell, 2009 March-July; 5030 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Jim O'Grady – Center for an Urban Future, 2007 May 24; 5031 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Urban Security: Engineering the Protection of Our Cities, Volume 1 – Conference Proceedings, 2003; 5032 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Bruce Niswander, 2007 January - 2008 September; 5033 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Demonstration Project: Engineering the Resilience of Specific Nodal Complexes within Cities, 2006 September-October; 5034 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Janice E. Perlman – Mega-Cities Project Inc., 1993-2009; 5035 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Noel Kriftcher – Sustainability Modulus, 2009 May; 5036 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Jennifer Weeks – Megacities, 2009 January; 5037 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Green Buildings Workshop – Polytechnic Institute of NYU, 2009 January; 5038 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Seminar on Urban Challenges, 2010 February 5; 5039 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Macarthur Foundation, 2004 November - 2005 January; 5040 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Multidimensional Infrastructure Simulation Center – Polytechnic University, 2007 January; 5041 (Box 46, Folder 14)